[
    {"question": "Katt", "answer": "Cat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hund", "answer": "Dog","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hus", "answer": "House","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bil", "answer": "Car","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bok", "answer": "Book","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Penna", "answer": "Pen","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bord", "answer": "Table","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Stol", "answer": "Chair","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Fönster", "answer": "Window","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dörr", "answer": "Door","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vän", "answer": "Friend","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Familj", "answer": "Family","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skola", "answer": "School","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lärare", "answer": "Teacher","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Elev", "answer": "Student","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Mat", "answer": "Food","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vatten", "answer": "Water","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kaffe", "answer": "Coffee","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Te", "answer": "Tea","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Frukt", "answer": "Fruit","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Grönsak", "answer": "Vegetable","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bröd", "answer": "Bread","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Smör", "answer": "Butter","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ost", "answer": "Cheese","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Mjölk", "answer": "Milk","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kött", "answer": "Meat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Fisk", "answer": "Fish","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ägg", "answer": "Egg","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Socker", "answer": "Sugar","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Salt", "answer": "Salt","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Peppar", "answer": "Pepper","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tallrik", "answer": "Plate","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Glas", "answer": "Glass","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kopp", "answer": "Cup","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sked", "answer": "Spoon","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gaffel", "answer": "Fork","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kniv", "answer": "Knife","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Säng", "answer": "Bed","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kudde", "answer": "Pillow","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Täcke", "answer": "Blanket","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dusch", "answer": "Shower","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Badkar", "answer": "Bathtub","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tvål", "answer": "Soap","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Schampo", "answer": "Shampoo","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Handduk", "answer": "Towel","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Spegel", "answer": "Mirror","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tandborste", "answer": "Toothbrush","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tandkräm", "answer": "Toothpaste","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kläder", "answer": "Clothes","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skor", "answer": "Shoes","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Byxor", "answer": "Pants","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tröja", "answer": "Sweater","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Jacka", "answer": "Jacket","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hatt", "answer": "Hat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Handskar", "answer": "Gloves","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Strumpor", "answer": "Socks","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skjorta", "answer": "Shirt","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kjol", "answer": "Skirt","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Klänning", "answer": "Dress","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Underkläder", "answer": "Underwear","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Mobiltelefon", "answer": "Mobile phone","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dator", "answer": "Computer","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "TV", "answer": "Television","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Radio", "answer": "Radio","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kamera", "answer": "Camera","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Klocka", "answer": "Watch","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tidning", "answer": "Newspaper","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Brev", "answer": "Letter","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Post", "answer": "Mail","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bank", "answer": "Bank","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Pengar", "answer": "Money","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kreditkort", "answer": "Credit card","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Butik", "answer": "Store","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Marknad", "answer": "Market","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Restaurang", "answer": "Restaurant","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kafé", "answer": "Cafe","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sjukhus", "answer": "Hospital","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Apotek", "answer": "Pharmacy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Läkare", "answer": "Doctor","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sjuksköterska", "answer": "Nurse","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Polis", "answer": "Police","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Brandman", "answer": "Firefighter","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Buss", "answer": "Bus","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tåg", "answer": "Train","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Flygplan", "answer": "Airplane","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Båt", "answer": "Boat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Cykel", "answer": "Bicycle","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Taxi", "answer": "Taxi","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Väg", "answer": "Road","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gata", "answer": "Street","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Park", "answer": "Park","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Trädgård", "answer": "Garden","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Blomma", "answer": "Flower","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Träd", "answer": "Tree","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hav", "answer": "Sea","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Flod", "answer": "River","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Berg", "answer": "Mountain","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skog", "answer": "Forest","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Springa", "answer": "Run","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Är", "answer": "Is","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vacker", "answer": "Beautiful","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skriva", "answer": "Write","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Var", "answer": "Was","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snabbt", "answer": "Quickly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hjälpa", "answer": "Help","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Blir", "answer": "Become","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lång", "answer": "Tall","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hoppa", "answer": "Jump","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Är", "answer": "Are","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Försiktigt", "answer": "Carefully","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Glad", "answer": "Happy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Läsa", "answer": "Read","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varit", "answer": "Been","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Långsamt", "answer": "Slowly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Stark", "answer": "Strong","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gå", "answer": "Walk","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Har", "answer": "Have","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snäll", "answer": "Kind","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skrika", "answer": "Shout","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kommer", "answer": "Will","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tyst", "answer": "Quiet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sitta", "answer": "Sit","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skulle", "answer": "Would","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Modig", "answer": "Brave","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Köra", "answer": "Drive","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kan", "answer": "Can","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Arg", "answer": "Angry","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Flyga", "answer": "Fly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Måste", "answer": "Must","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Trött", "answer": "Tired","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Simma", "answer": "Swim","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Borde", "answer": "Should","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ledsen", "answer": "Sad","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Laga", "answer": "Fix","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Får", "answer": "May","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Rik", "answer": "Rich","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bygga", "answer": "Build","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vill", "answer": "Want","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Fattig", "answer": "Poor","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lära", "answer": "Teach","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Behöver", "answer": "Need","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Rolig", "answer": "Funny","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Köpa", "answer": "Buy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skall", "answer": "Shall","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lugn", "answer": "Calm","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sälja", "answer": "Sell","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kunde", "answer": "Could","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vänlig", "answer": "Friendly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tala", "answer": "Speak","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skulle", "answer": "Would","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snabb", "answer": "Fast","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lyssna", "answer": "Listen","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bör", "answer": "Ought","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Svag", "answer": "Weak","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Se", "answer": "See","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Måste", "answer": "Must","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kort", "answer": "Short","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tänka", "answer": "Think","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Får", "answer": "May","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lång", "answer": "Long","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Känna", "answer": "Feel","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vill", "answer": "Want","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tjock", "answer": "Thick","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skriva", "answer": "Write","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Behöver", "answer": "Need","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tunn", "answer": "Thin","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Läsa", "answer": "Read","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kan", "answer": "Can","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hög", "answer": "High","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Göra", "answer": "Do","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skall", "answer": "Shall","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Låg", "answer": "Low","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Säga", "answer": "Say","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Borde", "answer": "Should","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Stor", "answer": "Big","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gå", "answer": "Go","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kommer", "answer": "Will","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Liten", "answer": "Small","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Komma", "answer": "Come","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Har", "answer": "Have","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ny", "answer": "New","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Äta", "answer": "Eat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varit", "answer": "Been","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gammal", "answer": "Old","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dricka", "answer": "Drink","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Är", "answer": "Is","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varm", "answer": "Warm","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sova", "answer": "Sleep","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Var", "answer": "Was","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kall", "answer": "Cold","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vakna", "answer": "Wake","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Är", "answer": "Are","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Torr", "answer": "Dry","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Springa", "answer": "Run","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varit", "answer": "Been","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Våt", "answer": "Wet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skrika", "answer": "Shout","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kommer", "answer": "Will","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tyst", "answer": "Quiet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sitta", "answer": "Sit","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skulle", "answer": "Would","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Modig", "answer": "Brave","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Köra", "answer": "Drive","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kan", "answer": "Can","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Arg", "answer": "Angry","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Flyga", "answer": "Fly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Måste", "answer": "Must","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Trött", "answer": "Tired","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Simma", "answer": "Swim","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Borde", "answer": "Should","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ledsen", "answer": "Sad","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Laga", "answer": "Fix","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Får", "answer": "May","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Rik", "answer": "Rich","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bygga", "answer": "Build","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vill", "answer": "Want","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Fattig", "answer": "Poor","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lära", "answer": "Teach","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Behöver", "answer": "Need","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Rolig", "answer": "Funny","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Köpa", "answer": "Buy","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skall", "answer": "Shall","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lugn", "answer": "Calm","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sälja", "answer": "Sell","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kunde", "answer": "Could","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vänlig", "answer": "Friendly","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tala", "answer": "Speak","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skulle", "answer": "Would","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Snabb", "answer": "Fast","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lyssna", "answer": "Listen","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Bör", "answer": "Ought","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Svag", "answer": "Weak","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Se", "answer": "See","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Måste", "answer": "Must","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kort", "answer": "Short","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tänka", "answer": "Think","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Får", "answer": "May","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Lång", "answer": "Long","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Känna", "answer": "Feel","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vill", "answer": "Want","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tjock", "answer": "Thick","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skriva", "answer": "Write","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Behöver", "answer": "Need","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Tunn", "answer": "Thin","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Läsa", "answer": "Read","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kan", "answer": "Can","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Hög", "answer": "High","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Göra", "answer": "Do","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Skall", "answer": "Shall","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Låg", "answer": "Low","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Säga", "answer": "Say","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Borde", "answer": "Should","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Stor", "answer": "Big","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gå", "answer": "Go","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kommer", "answer": "Will","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Liten", "answer": "Small","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Komma", "answer": "Come","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Har", "answer": "Have","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Ny", "answer": "New","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Äta", "answer": "Eat","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varit", "answer": "Been","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Gammal", "answer": "Old","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Dricka", "answer": "Drink","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Är", "answer": "Is","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varm", "answer": "Warm","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Sova", "answer": "Sleep","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Var", "answer": "Was","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Kall", "answer": "Cold","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Vakna", "answer": "Wake","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Är", "answer": "Are","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Torr", "answer": "Dry","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Springa", "answer": "Run","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Varit", "answer": "Been","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"},
    {"question": "Våt", "answer": "Wet","question_language": "Swedish", "answer_language": "English"}
]